I was actually in Montana not too long
ago and yeah one person and you can I
like my tan it was actually a fun trip
but you can always tell when you're
somewhere where there's not a lot of you
I found that out in Montana and in here
you know I can tell you know you tell
the stair the stair not from not only
adults the adults very good at hiding
that they don't see a lot of you in
person it's from the kids the stair from
the kids is always the same it's like
[Laughter]
is that Kobe they don't know they just
want to autograph that's all blessed a
heart blessed a hard I knew it when I
was getting on the plane I'm walking
down the aisle or the plane and people
are looking at me like no it doesn't
look like maintenance exactly like I
don't know how to fix planes at all
so I'm sitting in the back of the plane
tonight I relax man it's 2019 man people
go everywhere all the time bro relax
right and the captain gets home he's
like we're out to Montana we go on to
Montana
[Laughter]
anybody on his plane not going to
Montana
please exit now
sir
think I'm not sorry talking about but
like I said I had a great time in my
tent it was awesome when I got there
landed in the airport they had this huge
huge stuffed grizzly bear huge right and
and I'm trying to take pictures but
right next to the the stuffed bears this
old rustic dude right
and I say rustic not cuz he was old but
you ever seen somebody that looks rugged
you know sound like cowboy rugged you
know sound like they know how to make
cigarettes out of tree bark like that
time to do right so he saw me taking
pictures of the stuffed bear and he's
like I'm paraphrasing you wanna know the
trick smarten one of those things am I
I'm never gonna put myself in a
situation where I have to ask more like
I say I want concrete I don't
don't frolic I'm not a
not a wilderness person bro I stay with
buildings and walls and stuff he said
what you gotta do is you gotta have big
yeah I'm sure y'all heard that before
right they say you got babies it wasn't
well this is a worse thing to do in a
bear attack right I'm testing that
theory
I'm not that good of an actor I can tell
you that now
that bear would know at least definitely
by smell
I barely like you scared as hell like no
I could tell hey did you know drive our
comedy has their own app download it
right now to watch save and share clips
and you can watch my entire special all
2 minutes and 30 seconds I'm just
kidding it's actually longer than that
it's about 5 it's longer you know what
I'm doing
get it download the app and you can
watch sharing all these clips send it to
your friends your friends friends your
parents and their their friends and you
get the point